

# Jennifer L. Brown

Web Design and Development

816-536-4349 jennifer.l.brown79@gmail.com https://github.com/jlynn81

Web Designer and Developer experienced in the field of web programming, with skills in designing, development optimization of web applications and 12 years of experience in Information Technology/Security, Network Administration, Internet Security, Client Support Administration, and more.

## Qualifications

- Web Content Management
- Database Servers
- Technical Help Desk Experience
- Information Security
- GUI and Tools
- Excellent Problem Solving Skills
- Strong Analytical Skills
- Proficiency in TCP/IP Protocols
- Project Management

- Document Management
- Development and Design Principles of Process

## **Professional Skills**

- JavaScript, jQuery
- ActionScript, FLEX, Flash
- PHP, MySQL
- XHTML, HTML, HTML5
- CSS, CSS3
- DOM, FlashLite

- Python, Node.js, AngularJS
- Adobe Creative Suite
- Photoshop, Illustrator, InDesign
- Object Oriented Programming
- Responsive Web Design
- App Development

- Microsoft Operating/Office Suite
- XML, API
- GIT, Version Control Software
- Interface Design and Structure
- Digital Video and Audio CODECs
- MAMP

# **Experience**

United States Air Force August 1999 – June 2012

United States Strategic Air Command (USSTRATCOM), Offutt AFB, Nebraska Knowledge Operations Management Craftsman

August 2009 – June 2012

Air Combat Command (ACC), Whiteman AFB, Missouri Information Management Specialist

January 2000 – August 2009

#### Education

Full Sail University, Winter Park, FL, USA

June 2014

Bachelor of Science: Web Design and Development

Westwood College of Technology, Denver, CO, USA

Some Course Work: Graphic Design Some Course Work: Animation

March 2006 – June 2008 May 2004 – March 2006

United States Air Force Technical School, Biloxi, MS

October 1999 – December 1999

### Accomplishments/Awards

2014 Web Design and Development Program Valedictorian 2014 Web Design and Development Program Advanced Achievement Award Joint Service Commendation Medal, USSTRATCOM, USAF Air Force Commendation Medal, ACC, USAF June 2014 June 2014

June 2014 August 2011 October 2008